OLUWABUKOLA AJIKE FASAN

FRONTEND DEVELOPER

Royal Garden Estate, Ajah, Lagos State, Nigeria. 08080110323 oluwabukola.fasan@gmail.com Portfolio

SUMMARY

I'm a skilled frontend developer with 2 years of experience, creating user-friendly, responsive web apps. I'm driven by a passion for clean, efficient interfaces, keeping up with the latest tech, and working collaboratively to deliver engaging user experiences.

TECH STACK

HTML, Figma, CSS, Tailwind CSS, JavaScript, Typescript, React, and Next.

EXPERIENCE

Startup Hive, Lagos State, Nigeria (Remote) - Frontend Developer

January 2024 - Present

- Translating UI/UX designs into actual codes using Next.js, Tailwind CSS, Typescript, and Shadon UI
- Collaborated with full-stack developers, specialising in frontend development, database management, and testing.
- Contributing to software applications by designing user interfaces, implementing server-side logic.

Sabi Programmers, Ondo State, Nigeria - Frontend Developer

July 2023 - December 2023

- Translated UI/UX designs into actual codes using HTML, CSS, Tailwind CSS, JavaScript, and React.
- Built reusable codes and functional systems.
- Building the client's side of the web application.
- Collaborated with Product Designers, Backend Developers, and Project Managers to improve user experience.
- Working closely with backend developers to integrate front-end components with server-side logic.

Onract Limited, Manchester, England, United Kingdom (Remote) - UI/UX Designer

December 2022- December 2023

- Gathered and evaluated user requirements in collaboration with product managers and engineers.
- Developed UI mockups and prototypes that clearly illustrate how sites function and look like.
- Adhered to style standards on fonts, colours and images.

Stutern, Lagos, Nigeria (Remote) - Frontend Developer Intern

June 2022 - July 2023

- Using HTML, CSS, Javascript and React to create user-friendly web pages.
- Maintained and improved websites.
- Worked on a mini project and also collaborated with different learning tracks(UI/UX designers and Back-end developers) to build Citrone redesign project.

Zuri Inc-Ingressive for Good, Africa. (Remote) - Product Designer Intern

March 2022 - May 2022

- Designed a Mobile Management system for task management
- Conducted User Research on Logistics Industry
- Team collaboration on the designing authentication codes Library

EDUCATION

Federal University Oye- Ekiti, Ekiti State - B.Sc in Computer Science

November 2015 - January 2020 Second Class Upper Division - 4.39/5.0

CERTIFICATION

Software Development (Front-end	l
Development)	

Stutern, Lagos State.

2022-2023

Introduction to Android Mobile Application

Development

Meta, Coursera

2022

React Basics

Meta, Coursera

2023

Certificate of Completion (Product Design)

Zuri Inc., Lagos State.

2022

Mobile App Development

Women Techsters Program, Tech4Dev, Lagos

State. 2022-2023

Certificate in Introduction to UI/UX

Geneza School of design, Lagos State.

2022